ILR Press Article Reprints and Promotional Materials /4256
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR Press Article Reprints and Promotional Materials
1961-1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
ILR Press
/4256
9 cubic feet
9 linear ft.
Publications (documents).
This is an incomplete collection of article reprints issued by the ILR Press.
8059036
Box 10
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 23, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
ILR Press -- Publications; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations -- Publications
8059036
- Reprint numbers 1-91, 1952-1960. (Box 1)
  - The Unpaid Local Leader, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    ALL pamphlets/ booklets in collection are reprints of original documents
  - How to Prepare Training Manuals, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Legality of New Jersey's Antistrike Law, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Patterns of Participation in Local Union, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Conflicts within the Local Union, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Local Union Meeting, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Trade Union Wage Policy in Postwar Britain, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Indeterminateness of Wages of Semiskilled Workers, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Utilization of Older Workers, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Wage Relation in Australia, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Nationalization and Workers' Control in Britain and France, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - What the Worker Really Thinks of His Union, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Occupation and the Selection of Local Union Officers, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Some Problems of Communication in the Local Union (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Human Relations in Industry, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - An Industrial Problem: Australia's Longshoremen, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Interviewing for Organizational Research, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Government Regulation of Local Union Democracy, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - The NLRB and the Multiemployer Unit, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Interplant Wage Inequities, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Factors in the Unionization of a Utilities Company A Case Study, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Union Discipline Minority Rights and Public Policy, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Union Activity and Dual Loyalty, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - The "Close Shop" Controversy in Postwar Britain, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - "Resistentialism" in Applied Social Research, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Indian Trade Unions Since Independence, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Governmental Restrictions on Labor Mobility in Italy, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Psychiatry in Industry, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Social Integration, Attitudes, and Union Activity, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Newspaper Coverage of Labor-Management News: The Reporters' Point of View, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Education Principles and Training Manuals, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Human Relations Training and the Stability of Leadership Patterns, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Legal Protection of Labor in Contemporary India, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Wages in India, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Economic Development, Income Distribution, and Capital Formation in Mexico, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Interim Report of a Research Project in Mediation, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - NLRB Policy on the Employer's Duty to Supply Economic Data for Bargaining, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Interaction Process Analysis of Professional Behavior, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - The Vienna ICFTU Congress, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Notes on the Beginnings of Collective Bargaining, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Labor's Search for Its Place in the Community, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Interaction Process Analysis of the Mediation of Labor Management Disputes, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - An Industrial Psychiatrist Looks at Employee Communications and Accidents and the "Human Factor", 1955 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Foreign Affairs and the AFL-CIO, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Structure and Government of the AFL-CIO, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Engineers and Workers A Case Study, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Human Relations Theory - a progress report, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - The Maryland Public Utilities Disputes Act, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - The "Outsider's" Role in Field Study (Only one copy), 1956 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - The Interindustry Wage Structure, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Problems of Industrial Sociology, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Compensation of Industrial Workers for Jury Service, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Final Report on a Research Project in Mediation, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - A Study of the Process of Affiliation with Alcoholics Anonymous, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Role of Legislation in Regulating Labor Management Relations in India, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Postwar Wage Determination in the Netherlands, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Problems of Indian Trade Unionism, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Trade Unions in Malaya, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Labor and Nationalism in the British Caribbean, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - The Italian Labor Movement in 1956: The Structure of Crisis, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - On the Ranking Problem, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Identifying the Problem Drinker on the Job, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Alcoholism: Group Factors in Etiology and Therapy (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - The National War Labor Board: A View Against the Background of Grievance Disputes, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - On Asking Indirect Questions (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Dispute Settlement in the New York Longshore Industry, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Regulations of Employee Benefit Programs, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - British American Changes in Interindustry Wage Structure Under Full Employment, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Lockouts, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - The CIO Jurisdictional Dispute Experience, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Alcoholics Anonymous, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - The AFL in the 1920's: A Strategy of Defense, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Decasualization of Employment On the New York Waterfront, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Management Unionism and Public Policy On the Railroads and the Airlines, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - A New Bivariate Sign Test (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Indonesian Labor Relations in their Political Setting, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Social Organization and Alcoholism: A Review of Significant Research Since 1940, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - How Do You Know If the Informant is Telling the Truth? (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Automation-Challenge to Collective Bargaining, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Initial Experience in Operation of Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plans, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - "Situational" Interactions- A Worthwhile Concept (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Employee Relations Facts: Sources and Control (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Union Wage Policy in Heavy Construction: The St. Lawrence Seaway, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - I. The Personnel Dilemma: Profession or Not? II. Why I'm for Professionalizing, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Government Intervention in Emergency Labor Disputes in Atomic Energy, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Individual Rights in Collective Labor Relations (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - New York State Labor Relations Law 1959 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Vocational Rehabilitation, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Labor Relations Aspects of Industrial Medicine Cornell University Off Campus Conference, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - The Inevitability of Political: Unionism in Underdeveloped Countries: Italy, the Exemplar, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Intercultural Communication: A Guide to Men of Action, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Reprint numbers 92-189, 1960-1966. (Box 2)
  - The Evolving Work-Life Pattern, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Sense of Responsibility among Young Workers, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Labor-Market Aspects of the St. Lawrence Seaway Project, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - American Minimum Wage Laws: Their Purposes and Results (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Neo-Liberalism: An Analysis and Proposed Application, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Young Workers Speak Their Minds, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Agreement on the Railroads- The Joint Railway Conference of 1926, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - ICFTU After Ten Years: Problems and Prospects, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - How to Develop and Communicate Wage Payment Systems in the Hotel, Restaurant, and Service Industry (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The Behavior and Personality of the Labor Mediator: The Parties' Perception of Mediator Behavior, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Affluence, Collective Bargaining and Steel, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Labor Relations Law, 1960 no. 103 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - A Problem for Union Democracy: Officers' Attitudes Toward Union Members- 104, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Stability and Growth in the Postwar Italian Economy, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Comparative Wage Structures in the Steel Industry of the Soviet Union & Western Countries, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - The Use of Tripartite Bodies to Supplement Collective Bargaining, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Labour Commitment among Jamaican Bauxite Workers, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Economics and Technology: The Case of Soviet Steel (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The Horizontal Dimension in Bureaucracy, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Regulation by Visible Public and Invisible Private Government, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Arbitration of Labor-Management Disputes in Canada, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Labor Relations Law, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - On the Need for a Political Science of Collective Bargaining (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Waste not Profit not, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - The Church and Socialism, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Soviet Employers in the ILO: The Experience of the 1930's, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - The Sense of History and the Annals of Labor, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Ability of the Federal-State Unemployment Insurance System to Provide Benefits in Time of Recession (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - The Relevance of Labor History To Industrial Relations (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Dual Governments in Unions, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Some Observations on Sampling in the Construction of Price Indexes (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - The Institutionalization of Labor Protest in Tanganyika and some resultant problems, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Research and Writing in Industrial Relations- Are They Intellectually Respectable?, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Needs and Opportunities For Industrial Relations Research, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Labor Law & the Public Interest, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - The Labor Movement of Ghana: A Study in Political Unionism, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - The Italian Past the Future of Impoverished Nations, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - The Impact of Psychiatry on American Management, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Collective Bargaining and the Antitrust Laws, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - The Courts and the Development of Labor Policy in New York State, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Labor Relations Law, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Interstate Migration And Wage Theory, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Xerox Corporation A Case Study in Retraining, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Attitudes Toward Labor: When Blue Collar Children Become Teachers, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Leadership and Administration in the ICFTU: A New Phase of Development (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Hiring Arrangements and the Rule-Making Process in Certain European Ports and in the Port of New York (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Flexible vs. Compulsory Retirement Policies- Some Preliminary Findings From a National Survey of Commercial and Industrial Establishments (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Some Social Psychological Correlates of A Depressed Area (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - The Sense of Responsibility Among Young Workers, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Programmed Instruction, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - External Influence and the Determination of the Internal Wage Structure (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Supervisory Leadership: An International Comparison, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Twenty Years of Management Development: A Conference, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - The Historical Relationship of Liberals and Intellectuals to Organized Labor in the United States, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Labor: A Partner in American Foreign Policy, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - The Labor Unions and Puerto Ricans in New York City, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - The Collective Agreement and the Duty of Fair Representation, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - New York State Labor Relations Lac, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - The Chilean Labor Union Leader: A Pre;liminary Report on His Background and Attitudes (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Modern Industrial Relations Systems, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Labor Mobility and Wage Inflexibility, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Life Styles in Mobile Suburbia, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Apprenticeship and Skill Training: A Trial Balance, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Toward An Integrated Approach For Research In Organizational Behavior, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Basic Social Trends in American Socialism, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Socialist Sources of Pan African Ideology, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Negotiating A Labor Contract, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Sex And The Personnel Manager, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - For a Sociological Concept of Charisma, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Two Articles on Automation, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - New Light on Identifying the Alcoholic Employee, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Two Articles on The Discipline Issue In Arbitration, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - The Enigma of Section 8 (5) of the Wagner Act, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - The Public Employment Service, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - The Impact of Numerically Controlled Equipment on Factory Organization, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - The Engineering of Human Behavior in Industry: A Conference, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Reaction of Supervisors to Emotionally Disturbed Employees, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - New York State Labor Relations Law, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Motivational Constraints in an Industrial Retraining Program, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - A Field in Search of a Focus, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Americanization at the Factory Gate, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Some Correlates of Risk Taking, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Reducing Unemployment: Problems and Policies, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - The International Labor Organization and Japan Politics, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Resolving Dispute over Contract Terms In the State Public Service: An Analysis, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Changes in Productivity and the Skill Mix, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - The Impact of Technology and the Need for a Dialogue, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Broadening the Approach to Salesmen Selection, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - The American Way In Labor Education, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Labor Relations Law, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Cohesion Disunity in the ICFTU: The 1965 Amsterdam Conference, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Behavior in a Non-experiment, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Public Employee Dispute Settlement: The Wisconsin Experience and Collective Bargaining in City X, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Heroes, Homework, And Industrial Growth, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Reprint numbers 232-312, 1967-1971. (Box 3)
  - Culture Change and Stress in Rural Peru: A Preliminary Report, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Organizational Structure and Disengagement: The Emeritus Professor, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Labor Elite: Is it Revolutionary, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - International Trade Union Organizations: Structure, Functions, Limitations, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Role of Peasant Movements and Revolts in Development: An Analytical Framework, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Women and American Trade Unions, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Effects of Need to Maintain Face on Interpersonal Bargaining, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Managing Change: A Test of the Administration, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Strikes and Solutions, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Supportive Lockout, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Do Ideological Differences Have Personal Correlates? A Study of Chilean Labor Leaders at the Local Level, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - International Labor Organizations, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Social Security and Economic Development: A Quantitative Approach, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Good Faith in Labor Negotiations: Tests and Remedies, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Union Officers' Perceptions of Members' Pay Preferences, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Manpower and Wage Cost Trends: The Wage- Price Guideposts, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Implications of Fringe Benefits in the 1970s, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Personality and Organizational Behavior Studies, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Cloudy future for coalition bargaining, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Reflections on My Work, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Traditionalism and Modernization Movements and Ideologies, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - On Language and Culture, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - The Strike as a Professional Sanction: he Changing Attitude of the National Association, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Determinants of the Differences in Quite Rate Among Industries, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Realms of Thought and Organized Labor in the Age of Jackson, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - The Effectiveness of Reinstatement As a Public Policy Remedy: The Kohler Case, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Labor Waste in New York: Rural Exploitation and Migrant Workers, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - The Role of the U.S. Professor in Developing Countries, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Trends in American Life Styles, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Labor Relations Negotiators on Bargaining: Factories vs. the Schools, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - The Allocation of the Coast of Displaced Labor and Severance Pay, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - The ILO and Japanese Politics, II: Gain or Loss for Labor, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - The Effect of Blue-Collar Unionism on White-Collar Earnings, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Making Sociology Relevant: A Teaching-Research Program for Undergraduates, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - The Sick Role, Labelling Theory, and the Deviant Drinker, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Fact Findings in Public Employment Disputes: Promise or Illusion, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Imitation or Innovation Reflections on the Institutional Development of Peru, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - More on MAR-JAC (only one copy), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Creative Potential and Organizational Structure, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - The Contract Rejection Problem: A Positive Labor-Management Approach, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Authorization Cards as Valid Indicators of Union Majorities, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Interplant Transfer and Terminated Workers: A Case Study, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Historians and the Literature of he Negro Worker, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Toward More Comprehensive Human Relations in Industry, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Building Better Organizational Models, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - On the Application of Behavioural Sciences Research to Management Problems, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - The Role of Ceremonials in Organizational Behavior and An Empirical Study of Howard Becker's Side-Bet Theory, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Supervisory Training about Alcoholics and Other Problem Employees: A Controlled Evaluation, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Rural Peru- Peasants as Activists, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - The Economics, Politics and the Law: The NLRB's Division of Economic Research 1935-1940, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - A Response to Marginality: The Case of Migrant Farm Workers, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - An Empirical Approach to Work Behavior, Interaction and Rehabilitation, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - The Remedial Efficacy of NLRB Remedies in Joy Silk Cases, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Factors Influencing Subject-Observer Interaction in an Organization Study, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - No. 286 "The United States", 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Demand Characteristics in a Field Experiment, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Open Systems Theory in an Organizational Sub-System: A Field Experiment, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Labor Relations in the Public Service: A Unique Branch of Labour Relations Practice: The Japanese Case cae in Local Government, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Public Employee Bargaining in New York City, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - The Protected Rights of the Union Steward, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Internationalism in Eclipse: The ICFTU after Two Decades, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Employment and the War on Poverty in the United States, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Handling Crises in the Schools: A New Application of Collective Bargaining Techniques in Community Disputes, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - The Effect of Civil Disorders on Small Business in the Inner City, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - "Delabeling, Relabeling and Alcoholics Anonymous", 1970 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - "The Development of Deviant Drinking Behavior", 1970 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Union Rivalry in Detroit in World War II, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - The Labor Arbitrator's Role: Tradition and Change, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - "Attitude Change, Behavior Change: The Role of the Training Department", 1970 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - "Organizational Conflict and Its Resolution", 1970 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Structured and Spontaneous Role Playing: Contrast and Comparison, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Sheltered Workshops in the United States: An Institutional Overview, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Czechoslovakia and the Communist Union Model, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Economies of Scale in Sheltered Workshop Operations, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Philip Foner and The Writing of the Joe Hill Case: An Exchange, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Foreign Manpower Trained in the United States: Policy Implications of Non-Return, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - The Effects of Changes in Quits and Hires on the Length-of-Service Composition of Employed Workers, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - The Outcomes of Impasse Procedures in New York Schools Under the Taylor Law, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - The Impact of Employees Selecition Practices in Three Local Governments on Potential Black Personnel, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Some Correlates of Traineed Success In A Couples On-the-Job Training, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - The Analysis of Impasse Procedures In Public Sector Negotiations, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Reprint numbers 313-374, 1971-1975. (Box 4)
  - Reasons for Employer Non-Participationin Manpower Training Programs for the Disadvantaged, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - A Human Capital Model for Brain Drain of Foreign Manpower Trained in the U.S., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Management Training: Where Has It Gone Wrong, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Needed Research on the Social-Psychological Aspects of Disease, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Police Officers As Boundary Personnel, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Technology and Organizational Structure: A Reexamination of the Findings of the Aston Group, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Structure of Scientific Fields and the Functioning of University Gradate Departments*, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Organized Labor and Foreign Trade, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pigeons, Persons and Piece Rates, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)